<resources>
    <string name="app_name">YogyaCampus</string>

    <string name="campus_name">Nama Kampus</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>

    <!--    List of campus name data-->
    <string-array name="data_name_array">
        <item>Universitas Gadjah Mada</item>
        <item>Universitas Negeri Yogyakarta</item>
        <item>Universitas Islam Indonesia</item>
        <item>Universitas Muhammadiyah Yogyakarta</item>
        <item>Universitas Islam Negeri Sunan Kalijaga Yogyakarta</item>
        <item>Universitas Atma Jaya Yogyakarta</item>
        <item>Universitas Ahmad Dahlan</item>
        <item>Universitas Pembangunan Nasional Veteran Yogyakarta</item>
        <item>Universitas Sanata Dharma</item>
        <item>Universitas Alma Ata</item>
        <item>Universitas Kristen Duta Wacana</item>
        <item>Universitas Sarjanawiyata Tamansiswa</item>
        <item>Institut Seni Indonesia Yogyakarta</item>
        <item>Universitas Mercu Buana Yogyakarta</item>
        <item>Universitas AMIKOM Yogyakarta</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--    List of campus description data-->
    <!-- <string-array name="data_description_array">
        <item>Established in 1949, the Universitas Gadjah Mada (Gadjah Mada University) is a non-profit public higher  education institution located in the suburban setting of the metropolis of Sleman (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. This institution also has a branch campus in Jakarta. Officially recognized by the Kementerian  Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Gadjah Mada (UGM) is a very large-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 35,000-39,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution. Universitas Gadjah Mada (UGM) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor\'s degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 74-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. The acceptance rate range is 0-9% making this Indonesian higher education organization an extremely selective institution. International applicants are eligible to apply for enrollment. UGM also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, study abroad and exchange programs, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Established in 1964, the Universitas Negeri Yogyakarta (State University of Yogyakarta) is a non–profit public higher  education institution located in the metropolis of Sleman (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian  Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Negeri Yogyakarta (UNY) is a large-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 20,000-24,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution. Universitas Negeri Yogyakarta (UNY) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor\'s degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 60-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. UNY also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, sports facilities, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Founded in 1945, the Universitas Islam Indonesia (Islamic University of Indonesia) is a non-profit private higher  education institution located in the urban setting of the metropolis of Sleman (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian  Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Islam Indonesia (UII) is a large-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 20,000-24,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution formally affiliated with the Islamic religion. Universitas Islam Indonesia (UII) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor\'s degrees, master's degrees and doctorate degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 79-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. The acceptance rate range is 10-19% making this Indonesian higher education organization an extremely selective institution. International students are welcome to apply for enrollment. UII also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, sports facilities, study abroad and exchange programs, online courses and distance learning opportunities, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Founded in 1981, the Universitas Muhammadiyah Yogyakarta (Muhammadiyah University of Yogyakarta) is a non-profit private higher  education institution located in the suburban setting of the metropolis of Bantul (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian  Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Muhammadiyah Yogyakarta (UMY) is a large-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 20,000-24,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution formally affiliated with the Islamic religion. Universitas Muhammadiyah Yogyakarta (UMY) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor\'s degrees and master\'s degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 43-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations and students' past academic records and grades. The acceptance rate range is 30-39% making this Indonesian higher education organization a very selective institution. International students are welcome to apply for enrollment. UMY also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, study abroad and exchange programs, online courses and distance learning opportunities, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Founded in 2004, the Universitas Islam Negeri Sunan Kalijaga Yogyakarta (State Islamic University of Yogyakarta) is a non-profit public higher  education institution located in the metropolis of Sleman (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of  Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Islam Negeri Sunan Kalijaga Yogyakarta (UIN Sunan Kalijaga) is a large-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 15,000-19,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution formally affiliated with the Islamic religion. Universitas Islam Negeri Sunan Kalijaga Yogyakarta (UIN Sunan Kalijaga) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor's degrees, master's degrees and doctorate degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 20-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. UIN Sunan Kalijaga also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Established in 1965, the Universitas Atma Jaya Yogyakarta (Atma Jaya University, Yogyakarta) is a non-profit private higher  education institution located in the urban setting of the metropolis of Sleman (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of  Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Atma Jaya Yogyakarta (UAJY) is a large-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 10,000-14,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution formally affiliated with the Christian-Catholic religion. Universitas Atma Jaya Yogyakarta (UAJY) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor's degrees, master's degrees and doctorate degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 58-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. The acceptance rate range is 40-49% making this Indonesian higher education organization an averagely selective institution. International applicants are eligible to apply for enrollment. UAJY also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, study abroad and exchange programs, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Established in 1994, the Universitas Ahmad Dahlan (Ahmad Dahlan University) is a non-profit private higher education institution located in the urban setting of the metropolis of Yogyakarta (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. This institution also has a branch campus in Bantul and Kulon Progo. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Ahmad Dahlan (UAD) is a large-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 25,000-29,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution formally affiliated with the Islamic religion. Universitas Ahmad Dahlan (UAD) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor's degrees, master's degrees and doctorate degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 29-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations and students' past academic records and grades. The acceptance rate range is 80-89% making this Indonesian higher education organization a least selective institution. International applicants are eligible to apply for enrollment. UAD also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, study abroad and exchange programs, online courses and distance learning opportunities, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Founded in 2014, the Universitas Pembangunan Nasional Veteran Yogyakarta (University of Pembangunan Nasional Veteran, Yogyakarta) is a non-profit public higher  education institution located in the urban setting of the metropolis of Sleman (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of  Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Pembangunan Nasional Veteran Yogyakarta (UPNYK) is a medium-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 9,000-9,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution. Universitas Pembangunan Nasional Veteran Yogyakarta (UPNYK) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor's degrees and master's degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 9-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. International students are welcome to apply for enrollment. UPNYK also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Founded in 1955, the Universitas Sanata Dharma (Sanata Dharma University) is a non-profit private higher  education institution located in the suburban setting of the metropolis of Sleman (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian  Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Sanata Dharma (USD) is a small-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 4,000-4,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution formally affiliated with the Christian-Catholic religion. Universitas Sanata Dharma (USD) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as pre-bachelor's degrees (i.e. certificates, diplomas, associate or foundation), bachelor's degrees and master's degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 68-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations and students' past academic records and grades. The acceptance rate range is 20-29% making this Indonesian higher education organization a very selective institution. International students are welcome to apply for enrollment. USD also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, study abroad and exchange programs, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Founded in 2006, the Universitas Alma Ata (Alma Ata University) is a private higher  education institution located in the metropolis of Yogyakarta (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of  Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Alma Ata (UAA) is a very small-sized (uniRank enrollment range: under-250 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution formally affiliated with the Islamic religion. Universitas Alma Ata (UAA) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as pre-bachelor's degrees (i.e. certificates, diplomas, associate or foundation) and bachelor's degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 18-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. International students are welcome to apply for enrollment. UAA also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, financial aids and/or scholarships, study abroad and exchange programs, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Established in 1985, the Universitas Kristen Duta Wacana (Duta Wacana Christian University) is a non-profit private higher  education institution located in the urban setting of the metropolis of Yogyakarta (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of  Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Kristen Duta Wacana (UKDW Yogyakarta) is a very small-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 500-999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution formally affiliated with the Christian-Protestant religion. Universitas Kristen Duta Wacana (UKDW Yogyakarta) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor's degrees, master's degrees and doctorate degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 39-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on students' past academic records and grades. The acceptance rate range is 70-79% making this Indonesian higher education organization a moderately selective institution. International applicants are eligible to apply for enrollment. UKDW Yogyakarta also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, study abroad and exchange programs, online courses and distance learning opportunities, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Established in 1955, the Universitas Sarjanawiyata Tamansiswa (Sarjanawiyata Tamansiswa University) is a for-profit private higher  education institution located in the metropolis of Yogyakarta (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of  Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Sarjanawiyata Tamansiswa (UST) is a large-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 10,000-14,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution. Universitas Sarjanawiyata Tamansiswa (UST) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor's degrees and master's degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 68-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. International applicants are eligible to apply for enrollment. UST also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, housing, sports facilities, financial aids and/or scholarships, study abroad and exchange programs, online courses and distance learning opportunities, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Founded in 1984, the Institut Seni Indonesia Yogyakarta (Indonesian Institute of the Arts, Yogyakarta) is a non-profit public higher  education institution located in the suburban setting of the metropolis of Yogyakarta (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of  Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Institut Seni Indonesia Yogyakarta (ISI Yogyakarta) is a coeducational Indonesian higher education institution. Institut Seni Indonesia Yogyakarta (ISI Yogyakarta) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor's degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 40-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. ISI Yogyakarta also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Founded in 2008, the Universitas Mercu Buana Yogyakarta (Mercu Buana University of Yogyakarta) is a private higher education institution located in the metropolis of Yogyakarta (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas Mercu Buana Yogyakarta (Yogya UMB) is a medium-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 6,000-6,999 students) coeducational Indonesian higher education institution. Universitas Mercu Buana Yogyakarta (Yogya UMB) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 16-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. Yogya UMB also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, as well as administrative services.</item>
        <item>Established in 2010, the Universitas AMIKOM Yogyakarta (University of AMIKOM Yogyakarta) is a private higher  education institution located in the metropolis of Sleman (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Yogyakarta SR. Officially recognized by the Kementerian  Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi, Republik Indonesia (Ministry of Education, Culture, Research and Technology, Republic of Indonesia), Universitas AMIKOM Yogyakarta is a coeducational Indonesian higher education institution. Universitas AMIKOM Yogyakarta offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study table below for further details. This 14-year-old Indonesian higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations. Universitas AMIKOM Yogyakarta also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library, as well as administrative services.</item>
    </string-array>-->

    <string-array name="data_description_array">
        <item>Established in 1949, Universitas Gadjah Mada (UGM) stands as a distinguished and prestigious non-profit public higher education institution that is prominently situated in the vibrant and culturally rich region of Sleman, Yogyakarta. Recognized and accredited by the Ministry of Education, UGM offers a comprehensive array of bachelor\'s degree programs that span across multiple fields of study, including the humanities, sciences, engineering, social sciences, and many others. This esteemed university has garnered a reputation for its highly selective admission policy, which ensures that only the most academically qualified and motivated candidates gain entry into its rigorous and challenging programs. The facilities available at UGM are extensive and thoughtfully designed to support student life; these include a well-resourced library that houses a vast collection of academic materials, comfortable and modern housing options for both local and international students, as well as state-of-the-art sports amenities that promote physical fitness, well-being, and a balanced lifestyle. UGM is not just an educational institution but a vibrant community that fosters intellectual growth, cultural diversity, and personal development among its students.</item>

        <item>Founded in 1964, Universitas Negeri Yogyakarta (UNY) is a reputable and well-respected public institution that is strategically located in the dynamic region of Sleman. The university is dedicated to delivering high-quality education and fostering academic excellence. With a large and diverse student body comprising individuals from various backgrounds, UNY offers a multitude of bachelor\'s degree programs across numerous disciplines, ensuring that students can select a course that aligns perfectly with their interests, talents, and career aspirations. The university is committed to enhancing academic success and provides a wide range of academic support facilities, which include extensive libraries stocked with a wealth of resources, modern research centers equipped with the latest technology, and comprehensive sports facilities that encourage students to engage in both their academic pursuits and extracurricular activities. The community at UNY thrives on collaboration and mutual support, creating an inclusive atmosphere where students are empowered to grow and succeed.</item>

        <item>Founded in 1945, Universitas Islam Indonesia (UII) is a prominent private institution located in Sleman, which has earned a distinguished place in the realm of higher education in Indonesia. UII is dedicated to providing a comprehensive range of educational programs, including bachelor\'s, master\'s, and doctorate degrees across various fields such as engineering, business, law, and social sciences. The institution places a strong emphasis on supporting international students and offers a wealth of academic services tailored to ensure that all students, regardless of their background, have access to the resources they need to thrive in their academic journeys. UII is particularly proud of its commitment to academic excellence and its role in fostering a diverse and inclusive educational environment that prepares graduates for successful careers in a globalized world. The campus is equipped with modern facilities, including study spaces, laboratories, and recreational areas, all designed to facilitate a conducive learning experience for all students.</item>

        <item>Established in 1981, Universitas Muhammadiyah Yogyakarta (UMY) is a well-respected private institution located in Bantul that is committed to providing quality education and fostering a supportive academic environment. UMY offers an extensive array of bachelor\'s and master\'s degrees across various fields, including health sciences, social sciences, and education. The university prides itself on creating a nurturing and inclusive community that welcomes students from diverse backgrounds, and actively encourages international applicants to join its vibrant academic setting. UMY provides numerous facilities designed to enhance the student experience, including modern classrooms equipped with advanced teaching technologies, well-equipped laboratories for hands-on learning, and recreational facilities that promote physical health and well-being. The university is dedicated to producing graduates who are not only academically proficient but also socially responsible and culturally aware, preparing them for meaningful contributions to society.</item>

        <item>Founded in 2004, Universitas Islam Negeri Sunan Kalijaga Yogyakarta (UIN Sunan Kalijaga) is a distinguished institution that has made significant strides in the field of education by offering a diverse range of degree programs. The university places a strong emphasis on a selective admission policy that aims to enroll students who are academically inclined and passionate about their fields of study. UIN Sunan Kalijaga is dedicated to providing extensive academic facilities that support student learning and development, including libraries, research centers, and various study spaces designed for collaborative and independent learning. The university prides itself on fostering a nurturing academic atmosphere where students can explore their interests, engage in critical thinking, and develop into well-rounded individuals who are prepared to meet the challenges of a rapidly changing world. In addition to its academic offerings, UIN Sunan Kalijaga also encourages students to engage in extracurricular activities that promote personal growth, community involvement, and leadership skills.</item>

        <item>Established in 1965, Universitas Atma Jaya Yogyakarta (UAJY) is a prominent private institution located in Sleman, renowned for its commitment to providing an extensive range of academic programs from bachelor\'s to doctorate degrees. UAJY is dedicated to delivering high-quality education and has built a strong reputation for its comprehensive approach to student development. The university offers a variety of student services, including academic advising, career counseling, and extracurricular opportunities that are designed to support student well-being and success throughout their academic journeys. UAJY also features modern facilities, such as libraries, laboratories, and recreational areas, that enhance the overall student experience and create a conducive environment for learning and personal growth. The institution strives to cultivate a culture of excellence, innovation, and social responsibility among its students, preparing them to make meaningful contributions to society.</item>

        <item>Founded in 1994, Universitas Ahmad Dahlan (UAD) is a dynamic institution that has rapidly established itself as a key player in higher education, offering a diverse array of degree programs across various disciplines while actively supporting international applicants. UAD is committed to providing extensive facilities and services that cater to the academic and personal needs of its students, which include modern libraries stocked with a wealth of resources, dedicated study spaces, and recreational facilities that foster a balanced lifestyle. The university prides itself on its student-centered approach to education, ensuring that all students receive the guidance and support necessary to navigate their academic journeys effectively. UAD also promotes a vibrant campus life, encouraging students to engage in extracurricular activities, community service, and leadership opportunities that enhance their personal and professional development, preparing them for successful careers in their chosen fields.</item>

        <item>Founded in 2014, Universitas Pembangunan Nasional Veteran Yogyakarta (UPNYK) is a medium-sized educational institution that focuses on providing recognized degrees across various fields of study, including engineering, economics, and social sciences. UPNYK prides itself on its commitment to academic excellence and aims to create a supportive environment where students can flourish both academically and personally. The university offers a wide range of student services that facilitate academic success and personal growth, including counseling, mentoring, and extracurricular activities that promote a well-rounded educational experience. UPNYK is dedicated to fostering an inclusive community that values diversity and encourages collaboration among students from various backgrounds, ultimately preparing them to become responsible and engaged citizens in an increasingly interconnected world.</item>

        <item>Founded in 1955, Universitas Sanata Dharma (USD) is a private institution that has built a strong reputation for offering a comprehensive selection of bachelor\'s and master\'s degrees while emphasizing a selective admissions process. The university is committed to academic excellence and strives to create a supportive learning environment that empowers students to achieve their full potential. USD provides a variety of resources and facilities to enhance the student experience, including well-equipped libraries, research centers, and recreational areas. The institution fosters a culture of collaboration, critical thinking, and social responsibility, preparing its graduates to make meaningful contributions to society and excel in their chosen fields.</item>

        <item>Founded in 2006, Universitas Alma Ata (UAA) is an institution that offers a wide range of degrees at various levels, including undergraduate and postgraduate studies. UAA is dedicated to supporting its students with both academic and non-academic services, ensuring a comprehensive educational experience that meets the diverse needs of its student body. The university provides resources such as academic advising, career counseling, and extracurricular opportunities that encourage students to engage with their communities and develop leadership skills. UAA strives to create a vibrant campus environment where students can explore their interests, develop their talents, and prepare for successful careers in their chosen fields.</item>

        <item>Established in 1985, Universitas Kristen Duta Wacana (UKDW) is a respected private institution located in Yogyakarta that offers a variety of degree programs across different fields of study while cultivating a supportive academic environment. The university is committed to providing its students with the resources and guidance necessary to excel academically and personally. UKDW features modern facilities, including well-equipped classrooms, libraries, and study spaces, all designed to facilitate effective learning and personal development. The institution emphasizes the importance of community engagement and social responsibility, encouraging students to participate in extracurricular activities and service projects that foster a sense of belonging and connection to the wider community.</item>

        <item>Established in 1955, Universitas Sarjanawiyata Tamansiswa (UST) is a large institution that provides a wide range of recognized degrees across various fields of study, including education, social sciences, and health sciences. UST is dedicated to offering extensive student support services, which include academic advising, career counseling, and extracurricular opportunities that enhance the overall student experience. The university strives to create a conducive learning environment where students can thrive academically and personally, and fosters a culture of collaboration, innovation, and social responsibility among its student body. UST aims to prepare its graduates not only for successful careers but also for meaningful contributions to society as informed and engaged citizens.</item>

        <item>Founded in 1984, Institut Seni Indonesia Yogyakarta (ISI Yogyakarta) is a specialized institution that offers a diverse range of programs focused on the arts, including visual arts, performing arts, and design. With a selective admission policy in place, ISI Yogyakarta ensures that it enrolls students who are not only talented but also passionate about their artistic pursuits. The institution is equipped with essential student facilities, including studios, galleries, and performance spaces that enable students to engage deeply in their creative endeavors. ISI Yogyakarta promotes a collaborative and innovative atmosphere where students can develop their artistic talents, explore new ideas, and prepare for successful careers in the creative industries. The university also encourages participation in community projects and cultural events, fostering a sense of social responsibility and engagement among its students.</item>

        <item>Founded in 2008, Universitas Mercu Buana Yogyakarta (Yogya UMB) is an institution that offers a variety of recognized degrees across multiple disciplines while providing essential student services aimed at promoting academic success and personal growth. The university is committed to creating an inclusive and supportive educational environment where students can thrive and achieve their academic and professional goals. UMB features modern facilities such as libraries, computer labs, and study areas designed to enhance the learning experience and foster collaboration among students. The institution also encourages students to engage in extracurricular activities, community service, and leadership development programs that prepare them for successful careers and responsible citizenship in a globalized society.</item>

        <item>Established in 2010, Universitas AMIKOM Yogyakarta is a forward-thinking institution that offers recognized degrees across a range of disciplines, particularly focusing on technology and multimedia. The university is dedicated to providing a variety of academic and administrative services that enhance the overall student experience and ensure students receive the support they need to succeed in their studies. AMIKOM emphasizes practical learning and industry collaboration, equipping students with the skills and knowledge necessary for thriving in a competitive job market. The university features modern facilities, including computer labs, creative studios, and collaborative workspaces that foster innovation and teamwork among students. AMIKOM also encourages active participation in extracurricular activities, community projects, and professional development opportunities, helping students to grow as well-rounded individuals ready to make meaningful contributions to society.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    List of campus photo data using glides-->
    <string-array name="data_photo_array">
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/2166.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/2194.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/10191.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/2191.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/14313.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/2156.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/2152.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/10203.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/2205.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/17501.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/2224.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/2206.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/13251.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/14115.png</item>
        <item>https://www.4icu.org/i/logos-seals/17502.png</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>